http://www.notetab.com/privacy-policy

Introduction
Fookes Software Ltd (“Fookes Software” or "Company" or "We") respect user (“you” or “your” or “user”) privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. We recognize that the European Union (“EU”) has an “omnibus” data protection regime established pursuant to the European Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC) (the “Directive”) and that Switzerland has a comprehensive data protection law (together, the “Data Protection Laws”). Consistent with its pledge to protect personal privacy, Fookes Software adheres to the Data Protection Laws.
This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets forth the privacy principles that Fookes Software follows with respect to transfers of personal information from users to the EU and Switzerland, including the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the websites aid4mail.com, fookes.com, notetab.com ("Website" or "Websites") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.
This policy applies to information we collect: On this Website; In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website; When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
When we collect personal information directly from individuals anywhere in the world, we will inform you about the purposes for which it collects and uses your personal information, the types of non-agent third parties, if any, to which we disclose that information, and the choices and means, if any, that we offer individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of your personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when you are first asked to provide personal information to Fookes Software, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before we use the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us.
Information You Provide to Us
The information we collect on or through our Websites may include: Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website; Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us; Details of transactions you carry out through our Websites (and partner websites) and of the fulfillment of your subscriptions. You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk.
Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain statistical data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including:
Details of your visits to our Website, including:
traffic data
location data
logs and other communication data
the resources that you access and use on the Website
Information about your computer and internet connection, including:
your IP address
operating system
browser type
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection is Cookies (or browser cookies) and server log files. We do not automatically collect personal Information, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.
How We Use Your Information
When we collect information about you or that you provide to us, we will describe to you how we will use the information. Uses may include:
Personalization of the website (e.g. displaying prices in local currencies)
Customer support
Processing purchase data
In any other way we describe when you provide the information
Disclosure of Your Information
We have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We will use personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate and complete. We may disclose aggregated information about you and information that does not identify any individual without restriction. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
A complete list of all trusted third-parties (along with their respective privacy policies) who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business and servicing you can be found here:
Google, Microsoft, FreshDesk, ZingTree, MailChimp, HubSpot, cleverbridge, SoftWorkz, CrazyEgg, Liquid Web
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
You can review and change your personal information by contacting us to access, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us so long as making such change does not violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.
Data Security
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on secure and approved third-party servers. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.
Links and Files
Our Websites may contain links or information to other websites, which are provided for your convenience only. Fookes Software accepts no responsibility for any links, their content, or your use of them. Access to linked websites is entirely at your own risk.
Ordering
Aid4Mail sales are handled by cleverbridge, an online reseller for Fookes Software that provides secure e-Commerce services.
When you order our software, we receive your name and contact details. We keep this information for administration purposes only and will not contact you unless it is required to handle your order or to provide customer support or you have opted-in to receive our newsletter. We respect your privacy and will not share this information with anyone else.
To learn more about cleverbridge, go to www.cleverbridge.com. To read their privacy policy, click here.
Liability
FOOKES SOFTWARE AND ITS AFFILIATES WILL NOT BE LIABLE (WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN NEGLIGENCE, CONTRACT OR TORT OR BASED ON A WARRANTY OR OTHERWISE), IN ANY EVENT, FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGE, EXPENSE, LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUE, OR LOSS OR INACCURACY OF DATA, OR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, EVEN IF FOOKES SOFTWARE OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES ARE ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, IN CONNECTION WITH (I) YOUR RELIANCE ON OR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE CONTENT AND INFORMATION OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED WEBSITE, (II) ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED WEBSITE, (III) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THIS WEBSITE; (IV) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; (V) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON OUR WEBSITE; OR (VI) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO OUR WEBSITE. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED THE AMOUNT PAID BY YOU, IF ANY, FOR ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF OUR WEBSITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS THE DISCONTINUATION OF YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE. IF ANY PORTION OF THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY IS FOUND TO BE INVALID, LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
FOOKES SOFTWARE IS NOT LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY ANY HARMFUL MATERIAL COLLECTED THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, LINKS, OR DOWNLOADS. USE OF THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. CONTENT AND SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ‘AS IS’, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.
Dispute Resolution
Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to Fookes Software via our contact page. Fookes Software will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between Fookes Software and the complainant, Fookes Software has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the Data Protection Laws.
Compliance with Court Orders & Law Enforcement Agencies
Fookes Software may disclose personal information without notification in order to comply with a legal requirement, court order, or subpoena, or to cooperate with law enforcement or government agencies.
Merger, Sale, Transfer of Corporate Assets or Reorganization
Fookes Software may transfer information as part of any corporate merger, sale, acquisition, transfer of assets, or reorganization without notice. Such transfer will be on the basis of the continuation of all privacy rights set out in this document.
Terms and Conditions
Please refer to our Terms of Use that govern the use of our Website and contain disclaimers and limitations of liability.
Your Consent
By using our Website, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the E.U. and Swiss Data Protection Laws. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page.
Contact Information
Fookes Software Ltd
La Petite Fin 27
1637 Charmey (Gruyère)
Switzerland
Questions or comments should be submitted to Fookes Software Ltd through its contact form.
This policy was last modified on December 4, 2017
